ChronoMap
README1:
	ChronoMap is decided to be an IOS application for time management. Now the code is runnable on the latest Xcode (version 10.0) in macOS.

Authors: 
	Ruicheng Peng, Haofan Cui, Shusheng Song, Wenhao Li

Changelog:
	This is the first runnable integration version.

News:
	This is the first runnable integration version.

Install:
	Download the code file and open the .xcodeproj

Copying/License:
	All credits to the authors.

Bugs:
	When it comes to the pop-up window of adding event, user have to enter something (not blank) before they click “post”, otherwise the system will crash down. 
	Furthermore, because it is on a simulator, the keyboard will not appear automatically. You may click “shift+ command + k” to shows the keyboard then you will notice that when you click the text field of “time”, the number pad will show up, which means you can only enter number there.
	And there are still many functions is not complete yet and we are working on it.
